Cyril Johnson Woolen Company Photographs 6589 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Cyril Johnson Woolen Company Photographs
1920-1962
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Cyril Johnson Woolen Company.
6589 P
0.44 cubic feet
0.4 linear ft.
Gelatin silver print, photographs.
Photographs of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company's employees making wool fabric.
10061865
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, October 05, 2017
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, November 13, 2017
Scope and Contents
Consists largely of photographs of employees processing wool and creating cloth. This includes sorting and cleaning wool, spinning, warping, and weaving. There are several photographs of finished cloth being inspected. Also included are exterior views of the plant.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6589 F: Cyril Johnson Woolen Company Films 6589 G: Cyril Johnson Woolen Company Graphics 6589: Cyril Johnson Woolen Company Records 6524/011 PUBS: ATHM Textile Industry Publications 6605 P: Davis & Furber Machine Company Photographs
Bobbins (Textile machinery); Costume--Men--Main garment; Dyes and dyeing; Fiber preparation--General--Wool sorting; Male employees; Looms; Marketing; Spinning machinery; Textile fabrics; Textile factories; Textile industry; Textile industry--Connecticut; Textile machinery; Textile workers; Weaving; Winding and spooling; Winding machines; Women employees; Women textile workers; Wool; Wool fabrics; Wool industry; Wool scouring; Woolen and worsted manufacture; Stafford Springs (Conn.); Bishop, C. M.; Bridges, S. Willard.; Jones, J. M.; Kent, William I.; Mone, Ed.; Murray, Leo J.; Ott, George.; Russell, Edward J.; Sorenen, W. L.; Taplinger, Robert S.; Wilikinson, Edwin.; Winder, G. N.; Cyril Johnson Woolen Company.; Davis & Furber Machine Co.
10061865
- Cyril Johnson Woolen Company From the Air, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Aerial view of Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn., 1940; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Aerial view of Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Air Photos Associates, Inc., Hartford, Conn., photographer. Gelatin silver print, ca.1940. Image depicts an aerial view of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company plant in Stafford Springs, Conn., in the center of the photo; note the water tower with "Cyril Johnson Woolen Co." painted on it behind the plant. In the foreground appears to be part of the business district of Stafford Springs; housing is visible in the background behind the plant on both the left and the right. 24.5 x 19.25 cm. (w/out mount); 35.75 x 28 cm. (w/mount).
    Format: black and white photograph.
- Warp Dressing Room and Spinning Mule, 1920-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Warp dressing room, 1920-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Warp dressing room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, 1920-50?. Image depicts a corner of the warp dressing room in the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company in Stafford Springs, Conn., showing the warp threads being wound from a warping creel through a lease reed to the warping reel. 23.75 x 18.5 cm. (w/out mount); 25 x 19.5 cm. (w/mount).
  - Item 2: Spinning mule, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Spinning mule, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image shows one spinning mule in the spinning room of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. Davis & Furber mule. One male operator shown at far left. 33 x 23 cm. (w/out mount); 36 x 25.5 cm. (w/mount).
- Company Sign and Raw Wool Through to Finished Cloth, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Sign for Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn., 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sign for Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts the sign outside the company's building. Sign reads: Cyril Johnson Woolen Co. Fine Men's Wear "The Fabric's The Thing." 35 x 27.5 cm.
  - Item 2: Close-up of man sorting wool at table, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Close- up of man sorting wool at table, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts elderly man standing at table sorting wool; another man in background also sorting wool. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 3: Man carrying wool to wool picker, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Man carrying wool to wool picker, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts man carrying wool to wool picker (already full) in background of room filled with black and white wool on floor. 35.5 x 28.25 cm.
  - Item 4: Close-up view of man at warping machine, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Close-up view of man at warping machine, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts man working at warping machine. 35.5 x 28.25 cm.
  - Item 5: Close-up view of woman drawing-in, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Close-up view of woman drawing-in, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts woman drawing-in, part of the process of warping. Drawing-in consists of threading warp ends through the heddles in the harnesses. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 6: Close-up view of man standing at power loom, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Close-up view of man standing at power loom, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts man standing at power loom at Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 7: Two female employees inspecting cloth, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Two female employees inspecting cloth, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts two women seated at table examining cloth. 35.5 x 28 cm.
- Finished Cloth and Wool Processing, 1947-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Three male employees inspecting cloth, 1950; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Three male employees inspecting cloth, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1950. Image depicts three men standing at frames, examining cloth. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 2: Two male employees in wool sorting room, 1940; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Two male employees in wool sorting room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: George E. Meyers, Inc. Photographic Illustrations 12 Haynes St. Hartford, Conn. Gelatin silver print, ca. 1940. Image depicts two men at work in wool sorting room. Wool piled in large baskets throughout room. 32 x 25.75 cm.
  - Item 3: Man sorting wool, 1947; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Man sorting wool, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Photo by George Valentine Enell and Associates, Hanger 4, La Guardia Field, New York, N.Y. HAvemeyer 9-5411. Gelatin silver print, 1947?. Image depicts man sorting wool in wool sorting room, surrounded by baskets of wool. Copy A. 31.5 x 25.25 cm.
  - Item 4: Man sorting wool, 1947; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Man sorting wool, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Photo by George Valentine Enell and Associates, Hanger 4, La Guardia Field, New York, N.Y. HAvemeyer 9-5411. Gelatin silver print, 1947?. Image depicts man sorting wool in wool sorting room, surrounded by baskets of wool. Copy B. 31.5 x 25.25 cm.
  - Item 5: Scoured wool coming out of a scouring train, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Scoured wool coming out of a scouring train, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts man removing scoured wool from scouring train (at left). Scouring removes impurities from the wool, generally by means of washing. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 6: Male employee sorting wool fleeces, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Male employee sorting wool fleeces, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts older man sorting wool fleeces in wool sorting room. Another employee visible in right background. Piles of wool all over room. See item 7 and item 8 in this folder for close-up views of same man. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 7: Male employee sorting wool fleeces, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Male employee sorting wool fleeces, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts older man sorting wool fleeces in wool sorting room. Large bags and baskets of wool in room. Same man depicted in item 6 and item 8 in this folder. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 8: Male employee sorting wool fleeces, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Male employee sorting wool fleeces, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts older man sorting wool fleeces in wool sorting room. Large bags and baskets of wool in room. Same man depicted in item 6 and item 7 in this folder (from a different angle). 28 x 35.5 cm.
- Spool Room and Warping Machine, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Female employee at spooler, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Female employee at spooler, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts female worker at spooler. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 2: Close-up view of spools in spool room, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Close- up view of spools in spool room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts large spools in spool room. Employee pushes rack of spools in background. 35.5 x 28 cm. See item 3 and item 4 in this folder for slightly different views.
  - Item 3: Close-up view of spools in spool room, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Close- up view of spools in spool room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts large spools in spool room. Employee pushes rack of spools in background. See item 2 and item 4 in this folder for slightly different views. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 4: Close-up view of spools in spool room, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Close- up view of spools in spool room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts large spools in spool room. Employee pushes rack of spools in background. See item 2 and item 3 in this folder for slightly different views. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 5: Male employee at warping machine, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Male employee at warping machine, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male employee at work at warping machine; photo taken from angle of looking through threads of warping machine. 28 x 35.5 cm. Same employee visible in item 6 and item 7 in this folder.
  - Item 6: Male employee at warping machine, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Male employee at warping machine, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male employee at work at warping machine; photo taken from angle of behind the warp beams. Same employee visible in item 5 and item 7 in this folder. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 7: Male employee at warping machine, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Male employee at warping machine, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male employee at work at warping machine; photo taken from angle of looking through threads of warping machine. Same employee visible in item 5 and item 6 in this folder. 35.5 x 28 cm.
- Bobbins, Spinning Frame, and Spool Room, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Close-up view of basket of bobbins, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Close-up view of basket of bobbins, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts basket of bobbins in foreground; spinning frames visible in background. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 2: Close-up view of basket of bobbins, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Close-up view of basket of bobbins, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts basket of bobbins in foreground; female worker at spinning frame in background. Same worker shown in item 3, item 4, and item 5 in this folder. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 3: Female employee at spinning frame, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Female employee at spinning frame, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts female worker at spinning frame, with basket of bobbins in foreground. Same worker shown in item 2, item 4, and item 5 in this folder. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 4: Female employee holding bobbins, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Female employee holding bobbins, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts female worker holding bobbins in front of spinning frame, with basket of bobbins in foreground. 28 x 35.5 cm. Same worker shown in item 2, item 3, and item 5 in this folder.
  - Item 5: Female employee holding bobbins, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Female employee holding bobbins, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts female worker holding bobbins in front of spinning frame, with basket of bobbins in foreground. Same worker shown in item 2, item 3, and item 4 in this folder; slightly different view than it4em 4. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 6: Male employee at spooler in spool room, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Male employee at spooler in spool room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male employee working on a spooler in the spool room. 35.5 x 28 cm. Same worker shown in item 7 in this folder.
  - Item 7: Male employee examining spool in spool room, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Male employee examining spool in spool room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male employee examining a spool in the spool room. 35.5 x 28 cm. Same worker shown in item 6 in this folder.
- Dye Room and Weave Room, 1947-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Two male workers at dye vat, 1947; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Two male workers at dye vat, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Photo by George Valentine Enell and Associates, Hanger 4, La Guardia Field, New York, N.Y. Havemeyer 9-5411. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts two male workers at a dye vat of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Co. Older man on the right is Waldemar Ekstrand, dyer of fine wools. Photograph used in a 1947 advertisement. 31.5 x 25.25 cm.
  - Item 2: Visual check of scouring bath, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Visual check of scouring bath, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts closeup view of man doing a visual check of a scouring bath; see item 4 in this folder for the same man but at a wider angle. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 3: Male worker at dye kettle, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Male worker at dye kettle, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts man at dye kettler, either putting fabric in or removing it. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 4: Checking scouring bath, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Checking scouring bath, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts man checking scouring bath; see item 3 in this folder for a closeup view of the same man. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 5: Male workers at looms in weave room, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Male workers at looms in weave room, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts two men at work in the weave room of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. 35.5 x 28 cm.
- Power Loom and Cloth Inspection, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Close-up view of man working at power loom, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Close-up view of man working at power loom, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male worker at power loom in the weave room of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. 28 x 35.5 cm.
  - Item 2: Close-up view of man standing at power loom, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Close-up view of man standing at power loom, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male worker standing at power loom of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. 35.5 x 28 cm. Same man depicted in item 3 in folder 7 (on right) and item 3 in this folder.
  - Item 3: Close-up view of man standing at power loom, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Close-up view of man standing at power loom, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts male worker standing at power loom of the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. Same man depicted in item 3 in folder 7 (on right) and item 2 in this folder. 35.5 x 28 cm.
  - Item 4: Cloth inspection, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Cloth inspection, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print, 1960. Image depicts one male and one female employee inspecting cloth at the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. 28 x 35.5 cm. Same man shown in item 5 in this folder.
  - Item 5: Close-up of man inspecting cloth, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Close-up of man inspecting cloth, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts man closely inspecting cloth at the Cyril Johnson Woolen Company. 28 x 35.5 cm. Same man shown in item 4 in this folder.
  - Item 6: Matching fabric to swatches, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Matching fabric to swatches, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts three men examining finished cloth to see if the fabric matches the color swatches. 28 x 35.5 cm. Same three men shown in item 7 in this folder.
  - Item 7: Examining finished fabric, 1960; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Examining finished fabric, Cyril Johnson Woolen Company, Stafford Springs, Conn. Stamped on reverse: Burns Photography Inc. 3909 State St. Schenectady 4, N.Y. Tel. EX 3-3633. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts three men examining finished fabric; note the swatches to which the fabric has been compared in foreground. 28 x 35.5 cm. Same three men shown in item 6 in this folder.
- Campaign to Promote American-Made Wool Products, 1958; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: American wool industry leaders, Boston, 1958, black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 9)
    American wool industry leaders, Boston, 1958. Gelatin silver print. Image depicts four men at an American wool industry meeting in Boston, 1958. A full-scale campaign to promote American-made wool products is discussed by industry leaders (left to right) C. M. Bishop, Jr., Pendleton Woolen Mills, Portland, Oregon; G.N. Winder, Denver, president, American Sheep Producers Council, Inc. (he wears a tie that says "Eat Lamb Wear Wool"); Edward J. Russell, chairman, wool manufacturers council, Northern Textile Association, and William I. Kent, president, Kent Manufacturing Co., Philadelphia and new president of the National Association of Wool Manufacturers. An industry-wide meeting to launch campaign was held in Boston May 2 and 3, 1958. 23 x 18 cm.
  - Item 2: Between sessions of wool industry meeting, Boston, 1958, black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 9)